

A highly skilled and adaptable professional with a strong educational background and extensive experience in business analysis and web or mobile development. Proficient in various programming languages, frameworks, databases, and development tools. Demonstrated track record in optimizing business processes, implementing technology solutions, and building strong relationships with stakeholders. Shows versatility in mobile and web development projects through freelance experience.

#### **Contact**



+6281242705758



rey.undot@gmail.com



inkedin.com/in/rey-hermansesa680454b/

#### **Education**

Bachelor of Degree: University of Klabat, Major in Information Technology (2006-2011)

#### **Skills**

PHP, Dart, JavaScript, Visual Basic, Java, C++, C

CodeIgniter, Laravel, Angular, Flutter, Blade, jQuery Lib, Ajax, Express Js, NodeJs

MySQL, MongoDB, OracleDb, PostgresWinbox

Windows 7, 8, 10, 11, Linux

Microsoft Office, Figma, Photoshop, XAMPP, Invision

PostMan, NetBeans, Visual Studio Code, Android Studio, Visual Studio, Navicat, DBeaver

#### Languages

Indonesia, English (native)

#### **Work History**

#### Backend Developer | PT Jasa Marga, Tbk (Jakarta, Indonesia) | September 2022 -Now

- Developing an employee data service application named "Data Aggregator" based on SAP data according to user needs and implementing microservices, where the employee data application is divided into several service components
  - 1. Employee Data Api: This service provides CRUD operations to be accessed by various backend and frontend applications. It can only be accessed by authorized third-party applications with registered API keys. JWT authentication is enforced for each user
  - 2. Middleware Cronjob/Scheduler: This service is responsible for fetching data from SAP based on the changed date made on the previous day.
- 3. Cron Job Monitoring: This service monitors the success of SAP data retrieval in the Middleware Conjob/Scheduler service. It also facilitates users to anyalyze updated data in the employee data API service according to expected changes. Users can request individual or bulk data retrieval if the cronjob data retrieval is incorrect.
- 4. User Management Service: This service is created to manage user-related tasks such as password changes for subsidiary employees and setting default passwords to true/false for central employee

 As a FullStack to Developing JM Mudik application, which is designed for individuals or family for the annual exodus(mudik) during the Eid al-Fitr holiday, with predefined routes according to users needs.

#### Technology Stack

- Programming Language: Javascript

- Backend Framework: Express js and Typescript
- Frontend Framework : React and Next is
- CI/CD Tools: Git, Gitlab, Bitbucket, Jenkins, JFrog, Docker, Openshift
- Database : Oracle, Postgresgl

## Full Stack Developer | Food Butler Ltd (Jakarta, Indonesia) | February 2023 - Aug 2023

Developed a food order system for IOrder, Ibis, and coffee shops, connected with online payments using TrustPaymentand Teller Payment

#### Technology Stack

- Programming language : Php, Dart

- Backend Framework: Laravel

- Frontend Framework : Flutter

- Database : Postgresql

# IT Application Specialist and Technical Support | PT. BankBukopin, Tbk (Manado, Indonesia) | November 2013 – January 2022

- Maintained bank hardware (EDC, ATM), troubleshootedcomputers, maintained networks, and created roles for employees using MikroTik and Winbox
- Creating an App retirement calculator application to assist in calculating the retirement period and installment for pensioners.

 Developing an App credit administration application web to aid employees in verifying whether a customer is eligible for a loan or not.

#### Technology Stack

Programming language : Javascript,
Dart

Backend Framework : Express jsFrontend Framework : Flutter

## Web Developer | PT. Iah Games Indonesia (Jakarta, Indonesia) | January 2013 - July 2013

- Developed web teaser providing information about thegame industry.
- Created user login authentication, worked with the portal/core game using SOAP PHP for real-time gamerinformation.
- Created user login authentication, worked with the portal/core game using SOAP PHP for real time gamerinformation

Worked with PHP, CodeIgniter, PyroCMS, MySQL, HTML, CSS, jQuery, Ajax.

## Web Developer | PT. Sketsa.Net (Jakarta, Indonesia) | January 2012 - December 2012

Developed web based academic systems and onlineshops.

Worked with PHP, CodeIgniter, PyroCMS, MySQL, HTML, CSS, jQuery, Ajax.

## Web Developer | Klabat University (Manado, Indonesia) | August 2011 -

- Migrate Klabat University's Academic system.
- Worked in backend using CodeIgniter to build CRUD operations for student information.

#### Freelence

**December 2011** 

#### Full Stack Developer | June

#### 2023 -September 2023

Developed a member registration application for legislative elections in web and android

#### Technology Stack

Programming language : Javascript,
Dart

Backend Framework : Express jsFrontend Framework : Flutter

- Database : Postgresgl

### Full Stack Developer Developer | May 2023 - April 2023

Developed an overseas workforce application

#### Technology Stack

Programming language : Javascript,
Dart

Backend Framework : Express jsFrontend Framework : Flutter

- CI/CD Tools: Git, Docker

Database : Posgresql

## Full Stack Developer | March 2023 - May 2023

Developed a whistleblowing web system

#### Technology Stack

Programming language : Javascript,
Dart

Backend Framework: Express jsFrontend Framework: FlutterCI/CD Tools: Git, Docker

- Database : Posgresql

### Full Stack Developer | February 2022 – June 2022

Developed a mobile application for a church named Digital Church using Laravel and Flutter

#### Technology Stack

Programming language :PHP, Dart
Backend Framework : Laravel
Frontend Framework : Flutter
Database : Posgresql

## Full Stack Developer | November 2021 - December 2021

Developed a pensionary calculator named Calculator MPP, uploaded to the Play Store using

#### Technology Stack

Programming language : DartFrontend Framework : Flutter

Database : Firbase